A Guide to the University of Virginia, Student Council, Office Administrative Files, 1975-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia, Student Council, Office Administrative Files 1975-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/2/4.901
This collection consists of 900 items, which are about 2.9 shelf feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection is a gift of Student Council, 108 Peabody Hall University of Virginia on 1990 August 27.
Scope and Content Information
Topical files regarding allocation requests from student organizations.
Topics include but are not limited to: All Saints Anglican Church, American Bar Association--Law School, The Barrister, Buddies of Beaker, Campus Girl Scouts of the University of Virginia, Citizens Party, Dance Club, Drum and Beagle Corps, Energy Information Exchange, Grace Baptist Fellowship, Hispanic Review, Honor System Committee, Irish Cultural Society, Juggling Club, League of Student Voters, Mahogany, Medieval Circle, Muslim Student Association, Peace Education Network, Peer Alcohol Educators, Quadragon, Society of Human Potential, Students Against Reaganism, Vanguard, Whitewater Club, and Zeta Iota Chapter of Alpha Phi.
Contents List
- Abundantly 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Afro-American Studies Club 1978-1981 (Box 1)
- Aikido Club 1982-1984 (Box 1)
- Akindelas Fraternity, Incorporated 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Alert Students of the University 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- All Saints Anglican Church 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Alpha Epsilon Delta, Premedical Honor Society 1976-1984 (Box 1)
- Alpha Kappa Psi, Business Fraternity 1980-1982 (Box 1)
- Alpha Phi National Fraternity 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- American Advertising Federation 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- American Bar Association - Law School 1982-1984 (Box 1)
- American Chemical Society 1981-1984 (Box 1)
- American Institute of Aeronautics & Astronautics 1982-1985 (Box 1)
- American Institute of Chemical Engineers 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Amnesty International 1978-1984 (Box 1)
- Anti-Vivisection Alliance 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Army Cadet Rifle/Pistol Team 1981-1983 (Box 1)
- Army ROTC Pistol Team 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Army ROTC Rifle Team 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Army ROTC Special Training Group 1981-1984 (Box 1)
- Association of Education Students 1977-1981 (Box 1)
- Association of Residential Councils 1979-1980 (Box 1)
- Association of Student International Law Societies n.d. (Box 1)
- Badminton Club 1981-1983 (Box 1)
- The Barrister 1982-1985 (Box 1)
- Beta Gamma Sigma 1981-1982 (Box 1)
- Bible and Temperance Group 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Biology Graduate Student Club 1979-1980 (Box 1)
- Biomedical Engineering Society 1981-1984 (Box 1)
- Boxing Club 1977-1981 (Box 1)
- Buddies of Beaker 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Campus Girl Scouts of the University of Virginia 1977-1984 (Box 1)
- Cavalier Club 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Cavalier Kickers 1982-1984 (Box 1)
- Charlottesville A-Sides 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- Charlottesville - Activists' Coalition 1980-1982 (Box 2)
- Charlottesville - Hash House Harriers 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Charlottesville - Lacrosse Club 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- Charlottesville - National Organization for Women 1980-1982 (Box 2)
- Charlottesville - Socialist and Feminist Alliance 1982-1983 (Box 2)
- Chi Alpha Sorority 1979-1980 (Box 2)
- Chi Sigma 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- Chinese Martial Arts and Philosophy Club 1981-1983 (Box 2)
- Christian Medical Fellowship 1980-1982 (Box 2)
- Citizens Party 1980-1983 (Box 2)
- Coalition 1978-1981 (Box 2)
- College of Arts and Sciences Student Council 1978-1979 (Box 2)
- College Council 1979 (Box 2)
- Commerce Council of McIntire School of Commerce 1979-1982 (Box 2)
- Committee to Pave the Lawn 1980-1985 (Box 2)
- Cornerstone Concerts/Christian Concert Committee 1980-1983 (Box 2)
- Country Dance and Song Society 1979-1985 (Box 2)
- Court Square Dancers 1981-1983 (Box 2)
- Cribbage Club 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Curry School Graduate Student Organization 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Dance Club 1975-1980 (Box 2)
- Darden Christian Fellowship 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Darden Real Estate Club 1984-1986 (Box 2)
- Deliverance Crusade for Christ - "Love in Action" 1981-1984 (Box 2)
- Democratic Socialists of America 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Disco Dancing Club 1979-1980 (Box 2)
- Discordian Society 1979-1980 (Box 2)
- Drum and Bugle Corps 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Easters Alternative Planning Committee 1982-1983 (Box 2)
- Ecology Club 1980-1984 (Box 2)
- Egyptian Studies Association in U.S. and Canada 1977-1980 (Box 2)
- Eija Celli Dance Company 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- El Limited 1983-1984 (Box 2)
- Energy Information Exchange 1979-1980 (Box 2)
- Engineering Council 1979-1984 (Box 2)
- Entrepreneurs Club - Darden 1980-1985 (Box 2)
- Episcopal Association of St. Paul's Memorial Church 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Epsilon Delta 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- Eta Kappa Nu 1983-1984 (Box 2)
- Family Practice 1978-1981 (Box 3)
- Fellowship of Christian Athletes 1981-1985 (Box 3)
- Finance Club - Darden School 1977-1985 (Box 3)
- First Year Council 1977-1985 (Box 3)
- Forum for Critical Issues in Law 1984-1985 (Box 3)
- French Club 1978-1982 (Box 3)
- Friends of the Bayly Museum 1981-1983 (Box 3)
- Friends of New York Athletic Club 1978-1981 (Box 3)
- Gamma Nu Psi 1981-1984 (Box 3)
- Gamma Roses 1982-1983 (Box 3)
- German House 1983-1985 (Box 3)
- Grace Baptist Fellowship 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Graduate Economics Club 1982-1985 (Box 3)
- Graduate English Club 1979-1985 (Box 3)
- Graduate Nursing Student Council 1978-1982 (Box 3)
- Graduate Public Administration Students Assoc. 1979-1981 (Box 3)
- Graduate Student Association, Department of Environmental Sciences 1980-1983 (Box 3)
- Graduate Student Christian Fellowship 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Greek American Society of UVa. 1982-1983 (Box 3)
- Greeks for an Informed Electorate 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Ground Zero 1981-1983 (Box 3)
- Hang Gliding Club 1979-1985 (Box 3)
- Henson Defense Committee 1979-1981 (Box 3)
- Hillel 1980-1984 (Box 3)
- Hispanic Review 1980-1982 (Box 3)
- History Club 1979-1981 (Box 3)
- Honor System Study Committee 1980-1981 (Box 3)
- Hunger Project - UVa. Committee 1979-1982 (Box 3)
- Institute of Clinical Psychology Student Association 1980-1983 (Box 4)
- Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers 1978-1985 (Box 4)
- Intercollegiate Policy Analysis Council 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- Interfraternity Council 1979-1980 (Box 4)
- International Club 1982-1985 (Box 4)
- International Folk Dance Club 1980-1981 (Box 4)
- Irish Cultural Society 1980-1984 (Box 4)
- Thomas Jefferson National Affairs Study Group 1978-1985 (Box 4)
- Jefferson Sabres 1979-1985 (Box 4)
- Jefferson Society 1980-1983 (Box 4)
- Jefferson Tibetan Society 1982-1984 (Box 4)
- Jewish Law Students Association 1984-1985 (Box 4)
- Juggling Club 1981-1982 (Box 4)
- Kung Fu Club 1984-1985 (Box 4)
- Lampoon of the University of Virginia 1982-1984 (Box 4)
- Latin American Studies Association 1981-1985 (Box 4)
- Law School Film Series 1981-1982 (Box 4)
- Law School Karate Club 1984-1985 (Box 4)
- School of Law Studebaker Automobile Society 1980-1981 (Box 4)
- League of Student Voters 1981-1982 (Box 4)
- Legal Interest Group 1980-1981 (Box 4)
- Linguistics Club 1981-1983 (Box 4)
- Long Shot Productions 1978-1985 (Box 4)
- Lychnos Society 1975-1976 (Box 4)
- Mahogany 1984-1985 (Box 4)
- Mainstreets 1979-1981 (Box 4)
- Marketing Club 1976-1977 (Box 4)
- McIntire Chapter - American Society for Personnel Administration 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Medical Women's Association 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Medieval Circle 1978-1980 (Box 4)
- Monroe Rifles Color Guard and Drill Team 1979-1982 (Box 5)
- Motorcycle Club 1979-1980 (Box 5)
- Movement Against the Draft 1979-1980 (Box 5)
- Mule Society 1984-1985 (Box 5)
- Mulholland Society 1979-1982 (Box 5)
- Muntu Fine Arts Guild 1979-1981 (Box 5)
- Muslim Student Association 1982-1985 (Box 5)
- NROTC 1981-1985 (Box 5)
- North Grounds Football League 1984-1985 (Box 5)
- North Grounds Rugby Football Club 1983-1985 (Box 5)
- Nurse's Christian Fellowship of the University 1980-1982 (Box 5)
- Omega Rho 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Open House Hotline 1980-1982 (Box 5)
- Orthodox Christian Students of UVa. 1981-1983 (Box 5)
- Othermind 1981-1984 (Box 5)
- Peace Education Network 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Peer Alcohol Educators 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Peer Sexuality Educators 1978-1984 (Box 5)
- Phi Alpha Delta 1980-1982 (Box 5)
- Phi Sigma Fraternity 1980 (Box 5)
- Pi Sigma Alpha - National Political Science Honor Society 1983-1985 (Box 5)
- Political Study Group 1980-1983 (Box 5)
- Pre-Veterinary Society 1983-1985 (Box 5)
- Primi Lumi Society 1978-1980 (Box 5)
- Pseudo-Intellectuals Club 1984-1985 (Box 5)
- Psi Chi Honor Society 1980-1981 (Box 5)
- Psychology Club 1978-1984 (Box 5)
- Quadragon 1979-1982 (Box 5)
- Republicans - UVa. Law and Graduate 1983-1985 (Box 5)
- Restoration Ball Committee 1981-1983 (Box 5)
- Right to Life Committee 1980-1985 (Box 5)
- rowing Association 1975-1976 (Box 5)
- Running Club 1980-1984 (Box 5)
- Russian House of UVa. 1982-1983 (Box 5)
- Ryu Kyu Kempo Club 1984-1985 (Box 5)
- Sara B. Cicoli Angel Flight 1979-1981 (Box 6)
- Scuba Club 1979-1981 (Box 6)
- Sigma Alpha Epsilon - Virginia Omicron Chapter 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Sigma Gramma Rho 1979-1981 (Box 6)
- Sigma Sigma Sigma Colony of UVa. 1980-1982 (Box 6)
- Small Business Club 1979-1980 (Box 6)
- Society of Collegiate Journalists 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- Society for Human Potential 1980-1983 (Box 6)
- Society for Interstellar Conquest 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Society for the Promotion of Academic Fellowship 1984-1985 (Box 6)
- Society of Physics Students 1979-1983 (Box 6)
- The Sound 1984-1985 (Box 6)
- Southern Africa Solidarity Project 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Speaker's Corner Reality Movement (SCREAM) 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Student Alliance for Space 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Student Association of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints 1978-1980 (Box 6)
- Student Bar Association 1983-1985 (Box 6)
- Student Medical Women's Association 1980-1982 (Box 6)
- Student Musicians of UVa. 1980-1982 (Box 6)
- Student Organization for Safety on the Grounds 1981-1983 (Box 6)
- Student Planners Association 1984-1985 (Box 6)
- Student Trial Procedures Research Group 1979-1980 (Box 6)
- Student Virginia Educational Association 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Students Against Reaganism 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- Students for Anderson 1979-1981 (Box 6)
- Students for Carter/Mondale 1979-1980 (Box 6)
- Students for Clark 1980-1981 (Box 6)
- Students for Effective Honor System 1980-1981 (Box 6)
- Students for Fall Break 1984-1985 (Box 6)
- Students for Farley 1980-1984 (Box 6)
- Students for Freedom of Choice 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- Students for Handgun Control 1980-1985 (Box 6)
- Students for Hart 1982-1984 (Box 6)
- Students for Hollings 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- Students for Humane Honor System 1980-1982 (Box 6)
- Students for Informed and Constructive Change 1980-1981 (Box 6)
- Students for Juries 1979-1980 (Box 6)
- Students for Wilder Committee 1984-1985 (Box 6)
- Students International Meditation Society 1981-1984 (Box 6)
- Students to Retire the National Debt 1981-1982 (Box 6)
- Students Together Against Racial Separation 1982-1985 (Box 6)
- Style Company 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Surf Club 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Synchronized Swimming Club 1977-1980 (Box 6)
- Tennis Club 1977-1984 (Box 6)
- Thursday Society 1982-1984 (Box 7)
- Trotsky's Raiders Ultimate Team 1982-1983 (Box 7)
- Undergraduate English Club 1979-1982 (Box 7)
- Undergraduate History Association 1979-1985 (Box 7)
- Undergraduate Philosophy Club 1979-1982 (Box 7)
- Undergraduate Sociology Association 1979-1982 (Box 7)
- Union for Political Science 1978-1980 (Box 7)
- United Fellowships Council 1984-1985 (Box 7)
- United Students for America 1982-1983 (Box 7)
- University Bobs 1982-1984 (Box 7)
- University of Virginia Daily 1978-1981 (Box 7)
- Vanguard 1979-1981 (Box 7)
- Vegetarian Student Union 1979-1982 (Box 7)
- Victims Rights Advocacy Project 1982-1984 (Box 7)
- Virginia Bar Review 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Virginia Collegiate Services, Inc. 1979-1980 (Box 7)
- Virginia Law Weekly 1977-1983 (Box 7)
- Virginia Players 1977-1983 (Box 7)
- Virginia Rugby Football Club 1976-1977 (Box 7)
- Virginia Vibes 1979-1980 (Box 7)
- Virginians for Jesse Jackson 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Whitewater Club 1979-1982 (Box 7)
- Women's Lacrosse Club 1982-1983 (Box 7)
- Women's Resource Center 1981-1985 (Box 7)
- Women's Soccer Club 1980-1985 (Box 7)
- Women's Tennis Club 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Woodrow Wilson Current Affairs Assembly 1981-1983 (Box 7)
- Zeta Iota Chapter of Alpha Phi 1982 (Box 7)
- Zeta Phi Beta Sorority 1979-1982 (Box 7)